Luis Fonsi - Despacito ( cover by J.Fla )
Yes, you know that I've been looking at you for a while
I have to dance with you today
I saw, that your gaze was already inviting me
Show me the way and I will go
You… you are like a magnet and I'm metal
I'm getting closer and I'm setting up the plan
Just the thought of it raises my heartbeat
Now, now I'm liking it more than normal
All my senses are asking for more
This should be taken without a rush
Slowly
I want to breathe slowly on your neck slowly
Let me whisper things in your ears
So that you remember when you're not with me
Slowly
I want to undress you with kisses slowly
Sign the walls of your maze
And make your whole body a manuscript
I wanna see your hair dance
I wanna be your rhythm
That you to teach my mouth all your favorite places
Let me overtake your danger zones
To make you scream and forget your own last name
Slowly
I want to breathe slowly on your neck slowly
Let me whisper things in your ears
So that you remember when you're not with me
Slowly
I want to strip your kisses slowly
Sign the walls of your maze
And make your whole body a manuscript
Oh, I wanna see your hair dance
I wanna be your rhythm
I want you to teach my mouth
Your favorite places
Let me overtake your danger zones
To make you scream and forget your own last name
Slowly